(finger clicking)
(light thudding)
(air whooshing)
(magical music)
(uplifting music)
(air whooshing)
(door thudding)
(coin jingling)
♪ Ow ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Cha ♪
♪ Shoo-cha-choo-cha ♪
♪ As he came into the window
was a sound of a crescendo ♪
♪ He came into her apartment ♪
♪ He left the bloodstains on the carpet ♪
♪ She ran underneath the table ♪
♪ He could see she was unable ♪
♪ So she ran into the bedroom ♪
♪ She was struck down it was her doom ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ Will you tell us that you're okay ♪
♪ There's a sound at the window ♪
♪ Then he struck you, a crescendo, Annie ♪
♪ He came into your apartment ♪
♪ Left the bloodstains on the carpet ♪
♪ And then you ran into the bedroom ♪
♪ You were struck down it was your doom ♪
(upbeat music)
- Hey.
Come here.
- Wait a minute.
(gun booming)
(gangsters groaning)
(upbeat music)
- Hmm.
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ You've been hit by ♪
♪ A smooth criminal ♪
♪ Ow ♪
(ball clicking)
(cue thumping)
- Yeah.
(air whooshing)
(upbeat music)
♪ So they came in to the out way ♪
♪ It was Sunday, what a black day ♪
♪ Every time I tried to find him ♪
♪ There were no clues,
they're behind him ♪
♪ And they end up never knowing ♪
♪ Other suspect or what to expect ♪
♪ Mouth-to-mouth resuscitation ♪
♪ Sounding heartbeats, intimidations ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay,
Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ Are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay,
Annie, are you okay ♪
(upbeat music)
(gun booming)
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ So, Annie, are you okay,
are you okay, Annie ♪
♪ You've been hit by ♪
♪ A smooth criminal ♪
♪ Ow ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay ♪
♪ Will you tell us that you're okay ♪
♪ There's a sound at the window ♪
♪ Then he struck you, a crescendo, Annie ♪
♪ He came into your apartment ♪
♪ Left the bloodstains on the carpet ♪
♪ And then you ran into the bedroom ♪
♪ You were struck down
it was your doom, Annie ♪
♪ Ow ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Hoo ♪
♪ Ow ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Hoo ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Pow ♪
(glass shattering)
(finger snapping)
(surreal music)
- Ooh.
(piano notes jingling)
Shoo.
(finger snapping)
(foot tapping)
- Oh, oh, oh.
(crowd squealing)
Ooh.
(hands clapping)
Oh.
- Okay.
- [Crowd] Annie, are you okay?
Annie, are you okay, are you okay, Annie?
Annie, are you okay?
- Annie, are you okay?
- [Crowd] Are you okay, Annie?
(upbeat music)
- Whoa, that's cool, huh.
I taught him everything he knows.
- Oh yeah, right, you show me.
- Okay, sure, hold this.
(upbeat music)
♪ Ow ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay, I don't know ♪
♪ Will you tell us that
you're okay, I don't know ♪
♪ There's a sound at the
window, I don't know ♪
♪ Then he struck you, a
crescendo, Annie, I don't know ♪
♪ He came into your
apartment, I don't know ♪
♪ Left bloodstains on the
carpet, I don't know why, baby ♪
♪ And then you ran into
the bedroom, help me ♪
♪ You were struck down
it was your doom, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ Will you tell us that you're
okay, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ There's a sound at the
window, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ Then he struck you, a
crescendo, Annie, hoo, hoo ♪
♪ He came into your
apartment, dag gone it ♪
♪ Left bloodstains on the carpet, hoo ♪
♪ And then you ran into
the bedroom, hoo, hoo ♪
♪ You were struck down, dag gone it ♪
♪ It was your doom, Annie ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay, I don't know ♪
♪ Will you tell us that
you're okay, I don't know ♪
♪ There's a sound at the
window, I don't know ♪
♪ Then he struck you, a
crescendo, Annie, I don't know ♪
♪ He came into your
apartment, I don't know ♪
♪ Left bloodstains on the
carpet, I don't know why, baby ♪
♪ And then you ran into
the bedroom, help me ♪
♪ You were struck down it was
your doom, Annie, dag gone it ♪
♪ Annie are you okay, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ Will you tell us that you're
okay, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ There's a sound at the
window, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ Then he struck you, a
crescendo, Annie, hoo, hoo ♪
♪ He came into your
apartment, dag gone it ♪
(gun booming)
♪ You were struck down, it
was your doom, Annie, ow ♪
♪ Annie, are you okay, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ Will you tell us that you're
okay, dag gone it, baby ♪
♪ There's a sound at the
window, gag gone it, baby ♪
♪ Then he struck you, a
crescendo, Annie, hoo, hoo ♪
♪ He came into your
apartment, dag gone it ♪